cafebonappetit.com 2012-05-26

# Privacy Policy | Café Bon Appétit

This Privacy Policy is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used. Please note that by visiting and using this website you are accepting the practices described.

**Visitor Information**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is provided with a domain name and an IP Address. When a visitor requests a web page from within the Bon Appétit website, our servers automatically identify and log the HTTP request that is made.

This information reveals nothing personal about you. In fact, the only information that we automatically gather and log is as follows: the IP address of the site that may have referred you; your IP address; the web page that you may have linked to us from, if any; the product identifier for version and make of browser (e.g. Internet Explorer 8); the operating system platform that you may be running (e.g. Macintosh or Windows); search words or terms that are passed from a search engine (e.g. Google or Yahoo).

Bon Appétit has found it advantageous to examine visitor traffic so that we can ensure maximum compatibility for the various browsers and operating systems that visit our site. By analysing visitation patterns, referring URLs and search engine terms, we can strategically enhance our exposure across the Internet.

**Cookies and log information**  
This website does issue 'cookies' (these are small files of information which websites use to identify its users), however, these do not contain personal information. Bon Appétit does not share this data with third parties. You can disable cookies by altering the settings of your browser and the website will still function.

**What other information does Bon Appétit** **request?**  
We may also request your email address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to add you to our mailing list, or by your request to have someone contact you for additional information. Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested.

**Anti-Spam Policy**  
We enforce a strict 'Anti-Spam' policy that means we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party without your consent.

In addition, Bon Appétit will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. If you are a member of our mailing list, you may be contacted with announcements, news, portfolio additions, and new products or services.

With each email sent, you have the option of 'unsubscribing' from our mailing list at any time, thereby disabling any further such email communication from being sent. If you wish to have specific communications with a member of the Bon Appétit staff, you will be required to provide specific information that will be routed to the appropriate contact within Bon Appétit.

**Third Parties  
**Bon Appétit will disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary.

**Security**  
Bon Appétit uses all reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Bon Appétit reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of the Bon Appétit capital stock or assets to any third party. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Copyright Bon Appétit Management Company. All rights reserved.
